TONI ODUJINRIN

COMPUTER ENGINEERING STUDENT/ SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Email:

todujinrin@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://toniodujinrin.netlify.app

Mobile: 431 998 7779

GitHub:

https://github.com/Toniodujinrin

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/toni-oduiinrin-02a80b232/

SKILLS

JavaScript, Python
React.js, Next.js
Node.js, Express
MongoDB, SQL,Microsoft Access
HTML, CSS, Tailwind, BootStrap
Microsoft Word Specialis
Microsoft Excel

PROFILE

I am a computer engineering student currently studying at the University of Manitoba. I have a huge passion for software development, and I am experienced in building full stack web applications with the popular MERN stack.

Achievements

Dev club Hackathon winner: University of Manitoba (2023)

Projects

Timeline: This is a full stack task management application. Live demo: https://timeline-ten.vercel.app/ **Countries:** This is a front-end application for checking information on any country in the world. Live Demo: https://toniodujinrincountriesapi.netlify.app/

EXPERIENCE

Lead Front End Developer – **Ecommerce Complaints**

October 2022- January 2023

Led the development of the front end of website and worked partly on the backend code. Played a huge part in the early launch of the start-up.

Company Website Demo:

https://ecc-sandy.vercel.app/

Intern - FMA

November 2021 - March 2022

- Gained valuable experience working in corporate office structure.
- Learned about and worked with CAD software.
 Developed Soft skills like: Leadership,

Organization, Discipline, Paying Close Attention to details.

EDUCATION

University Of Manitoba. 2023-present

Computer Engineering

GPA: 4.2

Whitesands Secondary School.

Lagos, Nigeria

Grade: A+